[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He began as a top notch still photographer, specializing in  black and white  photojournalism. He is best known for his photo essays for Life magazine and for his 1971 film Shaft.", "correct_answer": "Gordon Parks", "incorrect_answers": ["Spike Jonze", "Lee Grant", "Spike Lee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the anatomy of cockroaches?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They have two ocelli, or simple eyes.", "They have two long antennae on their heads.", "They have large compound eyes."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor played Jody, a kidnapped British soldier held by an IRA foot soldier with a transvestite lover in the 1992 film The Crying Game.", "correct_answer": "Forest Whitaker", "incorrect_answers": ["Stephan Rea", "Adrian Dunbar", "Peter MacNicol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He made a name as a director of very fine documentary movies. His first significant film was Titicut Follies, a documentary that showed the problems at Massachusetts Correctional Institution.", "correct_answer": "Frederick Wiseman", "incorrect_answers": ["DonSiegel", "Gordon Parks", "Keith Gordon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This zodiac sign is ruled by the Sun.", "correct_answer": "Leo", "incorrect_answers": ["Aquarius", "Sagittarius", "Virgo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Victorian poet is the author of Porphyrias Lover, a poem written in the form of a shocking dramatic monologue?", "correct_answer": "Robert Browning", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Hass", "Robert Burns", "Robert Frost"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "German Sweet Chocolate is so named because it was created in Germany.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Typical for the animal cells only, lysosomes are organelles built in the Golgi apparatus that contain what type of enzymes?", "correct_answer": "Digestive enzymes", "incorrect_answers": ["Inhibitors", "Amylase enzymes", "Restriction enzymes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1963, Frederico Fellini made a classic film about a harried movie director who had lost his inspiration.  Can you name it?", "correct_answer": "8 1/2", "incorrect_answers": ["le Dolce Vita", "La Strada", "Blow Up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Color Purple, when Nettie is thrown off Misters farm and Celie begs Nettie to write her, what is Netties response?", "correct_answer": "that nothing but death can keep her from it", "incorrect_answers": ["that she cant read or write", "that she cant afford the postage", "that she is afraid Mister will find out"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Gerard Butlers character in The Ugly Truth promise he would do if his plan fails?", "correct_answer": "quit his job", "incorrect_answers": ["appear naked in his show", "start respecting women", "shave his head"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie, which tells the story of a black private detective, was released in 1971 and starred Richard Roundtree, Moses Gunn and Christopher St. John.", "correct_answer": "Shaft", "incorrect_answers": ["Numbers", "Seven", "Shafts Big Score"]}]